44 - you said it correctly and soche -
44 - это вы правильно сказали а соче -
this is ffff oh when do they say that Yes and ffn a
это фффф о когда же так говорят Да а ффн
fn fifty-fifth that fifty-fifth is
а фн пятьдесят пятый что пятьдесят пятый
correct Oh well, you are quite fast Yes by
правильно О ну вы довольно быст Да по
analogy Hello
аналогии Здравствуйте
Gent I'm from the city of Cowes my name is ADS Where are you
джент я из города каус зовут Меня АДС Вы
from Good afternoon And me  name is Alexey
откуда Добрый день А меня зовут Алексей
I'm from St. Petersburg I
Я из санкт-петербурга я там
live there It's cool and where did you come to St. Petersburg
живу Прикольно а в санкт-петербург
Where did I actually
откуда попали Как откуда я вообще-то там
live there all my life I
живу всю жизнь Я там
was born there So you should probably play a song
родился Так вам песенку наверное сыграть
better watch I'm a teacher of the
лучше смотрите Я преподаватель
Lithuanian language and I'm wondering I
литовского языка и мне интересно я
had an argument with a friend today  I say that
сегодня поспорил с другом Я говорю что
Russians don’t know the Lithuanian language at all
россияне вообще не знают литовский язык
and for n is not consonant, he says that he
и для н не созвучный он говорит что он
was in Russia and spoke Lithuanian and
был в России и говорил по-литовски и
people understood him a little. So I’m
люди его немного Понимали Вот мне
interested, you can read the word in
интересно можете прочитать слово на
Lithuanian and say what it means,
литовском и сказать что оно означает
try to understand Yes, but here  this is
попробовать понять Да вот а вот это ну
even interesting, well, if you Read it,
даже интересно ну если Прочитать то
Ir Yes, but what does it
Ир Да но что
mean absolutely a Try if
обозначает абсолютно а Попробуйте если
you repeat it quickly in a consonant
быстро его повторить вы в созвучное
Russian word, you
русское слово
will hear something somehow it’s cool because it
услышите что-то как-то это круто бо
hurts Yes, perhaps I don’t know anything about
больно уж Да пожалуй не что не зна вот с
English, but English would be more interesting  to be
английским бы вот английский интереснее
honest, this word is the
честно говоря это слово Это слово оно
same as in Russia. It’s just that we
так же как и в России Просто у нас
don’t write vowels in
гласные не пишутся на
writing. And this word in Russian is exactly
письме А это слово в русском языке точно
the same. It would be better if it was the same.
такое же Вот лучше бы это само
You taught me
Английский вы мне преподали вот честно
English. To be honest, it would be nice to
говоря вот английский бы неплохо бы
improve my English.  I also
подтянуть английский Я английский тоже
teach English You can count I want to
типа преподаю Можете посчитать Я хочу
rate your pronunciation from one to
оценить ваше произношение от одного до
20 in English Read namely from
20 по-английски Прочитайте а именно от
one to 20 now I
одного до 20 сейчас я
feel I Guess You will Root My
чувствую I Guess You will Root My
pronunciation it seems like that But
pronunciation it seems like that But
anyway I will Try Let's Go One two 3 F F
anyway I will Try Let's Go One two 3 F F
Si 7 8 N 10 El
Si 7 8 N 10 El
12 a 1 14
12 а 1 14
kind of
вроде
like By the way, I forgot, I even need to tighten up the
как Кстати подзабыл надо подтягивать он
numeral to 20, and then somehow I
даже уж числительный до 20 и то как-то
need to tighten up the English language of something.
надо надо подтянуть англиски чтото А
Let me
давайте я вам буду
tell you in English and you will
называть по-английски а вы будете
translate it into Russian. Oh, this  it’s difficult to
переводить на русский Ох это сложно
try interesting Chust I’ll fail in a minute
попробовать интересно Чуст сечас завалю
let’s try and well sot it’s just
попробуем а ну сот это просто
nun
нун
fn Well, not something, to be honest, I don’t
фн Ну вот не что-то честно говоря не
know something like this
знаю что-то как это
144 not 144 A 144 Ordinal number
144 не 144 А 144 Порядковый числительный
Typhus yes
Тиф да
Oh even so, something I don’t even know
О даже так вот что-то я даже не знаю вот
44 - you said it correctly and forty
44 - это вы правильно сказали а соро
four - that's ffff oh when do they say that
четв - это фффф о когда же так говорят
yes
да
and
а
an psy py psia fifth is correct Oh well, you're
ан пся пй пся пятый правильно О ну вы
pretty quick and by analogy it's just that at
довольно быстро да по аналогии просто в
school they usually study first second
школе обычно там изучают первый второй
third fourth and that's all And then
третий четвёртый да и всё А дальше
ordinal numbers  they don’t study and there, in
порядковые числительные не изучают а там
my opinion, it’s
по-моему
added in my opinion. It’s simple. This is
добавляется по-моему Там просто Это это
this, this is up to ten If it goes yes And if
вот это до десятка Если идт да А если
it goes more than twenty then uh no
идут больше двадцатки да то ээ нет
more juice from juice Yes they begin
больше сока от сока Да начинают
uh specific names of ordinal
ээ специфические названия порядковых
numbers this well this is uh
числительных это ну это ээ сорок
forty-four foti ffn  Yes, the fifty-fifth
четвёртый фоти ффн Да пятьдесят пятый -
is fifty ffn Wow, I didn’t even know,
это фифти ффн Ух ты я и не знал Вам
thank you. By the way, Honestly speaking, this is
спасибо Кстати Чесно говоря для меня это
a discovery for me. Yes, I didn’t know that. Unfortunately,
открытие Да этого я не знал К сожалению
Uh-huh. Yes, we didn’t go through that; we weren’t
Угу Да это мы не проходили это нам не
asked; we weren’t asked; and I didn’t
задавали нам не задавали да и сам не
go through something myself.  somehow
прошёл что-то как-то
it’s good, try to put together a
а хорошо вот Попробуйте сложить
sentence, the war was in the
предложение война была в сочет
year in
году в
Soche Sochi, we just chtoli order
соче сочей мы же только чтоли поряд
and
а
well, if 44 apples are 44 And if
хорошо вот если 44 яблока это 44 А если
soche then it’s FF
соче то это ФФ
yes yes order Okay, now say there for
да да поряд Хорошо а теперь скажите там
example
например
let’s let it be with the war  there will be a war
давайте так пусть с войной будет война
going on from what year to
шла с со чего года по
55 the war was going on
55 война именно шла
yes Well, maybe I’ll translate it as it was From
да Ну может переведу как была was From
uh
ээ
and forty-four everything yes forty-
а сорок четвёртого всё да сорок
fourth order from forty-four to
четвёртый порядка с сорок четвёртого по
fifty-fifth
пятьдесят пятый
fn eh f
фн э
ffn it turns out
ф ффн получается
fn
фн
ffn forty-fifth Well, like fifty, not me
ффн сорок пятый Ну как фифти не я же
said fifty-five, I specifically
сказал по пятьдесят пятый я специально
gave it not forty-five, but fifty-five, like a
дал не соро пятый а пятьдесят пятый типа
virtual war, I’ve lowered my head here already, I’ve
виртуальная война потупил тут уже я
blunted it, it means okay Well, yes, there’s some kind of
затупил значит ладно Ну да тут какая-то
good, but yes, here’s the p you
а хорошо а вот да вот со п вы правильно
designed correctly 45 Let’s have fun The
сконструировали 45 Давайте поте ска
victory over Germany was at forty  fifth
Победа над Германией была в сорок пятом
year Well, how interesting to listen to by the way,
году Ну как интересно кстати
yes Well then I would say so then it
да Ну тогда я бы сказал бы так тогда
doesn’t work out
не получается
germany germany just Victory would
германи германи просто Победа бы Победа
have been a victory
была
year
году
germany ska
германие ска
[music]
[музыка]
a little different and by the way how to
немножко подругому а кстати а как
say it correctly Well here I want
правильно сказать Ну вот тут тут я хочу
you to guess because  you
чтобы вы догадались потому что вы
walk normally You think correctly
нормально идёте Вы правильно мыслите У
You have you know that the most important thing
вас есть у вас знаете что самое главное
is the feeling of language Because
есть ощущение языка Потому что вот
many people when they speak incorrectly
многие люди когда неправильно говорят
they say and you all understand that Well,
они говорят и всё вы понимаете что Ну
well, this construction doesn’t work, you
вот ну не идёт эта конструкция это у вас
have it, it’s called in linguistics
есть это называется в лингвистике
grammatical sense  here you have it,
грамматическое чутьё вот оно у вас есть
well, it’s somehow not verbatim Yes, it
ну оно как-то не дословно Да там как-то
must be somehow different
по-другому должно быть
I don’t know which preposition is better I
Я не знаю какой предлог лучше Вот
can’t
предлог не могу
think of a preposition but look But the ordinal
придумать а А смотрите А вот Порядковый
number is above 40 and p here 40 and 50 I’m
числительный выше 40 и п вот 40 и 50 Я
like that  I understand you have mastered And for example 67 here is the
так понимаю вы освоили А например 67 вот
eighty-eighth as it will be Well, I would
восемьдесят восьмой как будет Ну я бы
still say so if according to your taxes
так сказал всё-таки если по вашей налоги
then
тогда
these uh not these are not suitable these
эти э не эти не годится эти
these it turns out not No no this is hey - this is
эти получается не Нет нет это э й - это
where the fricative vowel goes changes
во там идёт фрикативное гласное меняется
in the eighty-eighth  when they say Yes
в восемьдесят восьмой когда говорят Да
This is oti eighty-eighth - this is oti
Это оти восемьдесят восьмой - это оти Да
Yes, for example, uh, eighty-fifth oti
вот например ээ восемьдесят пятый оти
fofan, eighty-fifth oti fofan Yes oti
фофан восемьдесят пятый оти фофан Да оти
Yes, the eighty-eighth ten in
Да восьмидесятый восьмой десяток в
ordinal numbers is oti Yes, here is the
порядковых числительных - это оти Да вот
eighty-fourth oh oh
восемьдесят четвёртый э ой
I'm already confused,
Я уже запутался
why
че
yes And for example, the eighty-eighth -  this is
да А например восемьдесят восьмой - это
oti oten oti oten oten oten Yes, yes, this is
оти отен оти отен отен отен Да да это
something too complicated, perhaps there’s
что-то как-то слишком сложно пожалуй тут
already something here. But still, I’d be more
уже да что-то А вот всё-таки мне
interested in something else, I’d like to figure it out after
интересней бы другое бы разобраться
all. That’s exactly the victory
вс-таки Вот как раз вот именно победа
over Germany, that’s it  everyone is interested in
над Германией вот вот это всё интересует
how to still say if there is a victory over
вот как всё-таки сказать если победа над
Germany or any other side.
Германией или там любой другой стороны
The fact is that in the English language there is no
Дело в том что в английском языке нету
such construction; there is a victory over something;
такой конструкции там победа над чем-то
in the Russian language there is such a construction in the
это в русском языке такая конструкция в
English language; there is such a thing; Germany
английском языке есть такое там Германия
was defeated by the allies.  so it
была повержена союзниками Вот так надо
was necessary to say And yes, exactly you are
было сказать А да точно Вы
right, it’s defeated, so
правы именно повержен так повержен
defeated Well, yes, it’s lost, you can say
Ну да проиграно можно сказать
that it’s a little bit not that
что это как бы немножко не
it’s
то это
lost, as if you lost it
потеряно как будто вы её потеряли
by accident and lost it
случайно шли и потеряли
altogether with
вообще с
Lose too Well, this is not a game but
Проигрывать тоже Ну это Это не игра по
this is when The Game  Yes, the game then You can
это когда The Game Да игра тогда Можно
Wi And here it’s a little different Well then I don’t
Wi А тут немножко другое Ну тогда не
know now, speaking then I’m already giving up
знаю сечас говоря тогда я уже сдаюсь
I guess I don’t know Well Think about the analogues,
пожалуй не знаю Ну Подумайте аналоги
tell me Yes, that’s correct, and I
скажите вы Да как правильно вот а я
’ll listen Let’s start with this verb starting
послушаю Давайте начинается этот глагол
with yes and yes, well, no, well, not,
на д а да ну не ну не ну
even Cool Well  Yes,
даже Круто Ну да
build Nestro, too, look at the
строи нестро тоже на вот смотрите
semantics of this verb Destroy Yes, this is
семантика этого глагола Дестрой Да это
Destroy to destroy Yes, here, too,
Дестрой раз рушить Да вот тут тоже
the verb with D begins, but a little
глагол на Д начинается но немножко
different guess sting on, well, well, not Del,
другой гадать жал на на ну да ну не Del
exactly somehow it’s a hundred not Del, not Del, not
точно как-то это сто не Del не Del не
Del, not Del  this is deleted but on exactly
Del не Del это удалена но на на именно
The Victor and The vict yes vikri - This is a
The Victor а The vict да викри - Это
victory and The Victory is as if
победа а The Victory - это как бы
defeated, on the contrary it turns out in
побеждена наоборот получается в
English there is yes and in the same way from the
английском языке есть да а во как от
word like destru Yes destruction
слово вот так как дестру Да деструкция
yes this is structuring and destruction
да это структурирование а деструкция -
is the other way around  also since yes devik like yes
это наоборот также раз да девик типа да
this is a loss in the
это проигрыш в
war yes
войне да
now
теперь
say allies
скажите союзники
Let’s get
Давайте получается
US allies you need to say allies and
US союзники нужно сказать союзники а
allies exactly the
союзники именно
Union I remember like
а Союз помню вроде
how military allies with the letter e
какда военные союзники на букву э
are written like this with the letter e military
пишется так на букву э военные
allies Alliance is probably some kind
союзники Альянс наверное какой-нибудь
That’s what-  then this is consonant with the word
Вот вот что-то такое созвучно со словом
alliance alliance somehow well yes
альянс альянс как-нибудь там ну да
Alliance Of course they are ANS - it’s more
Альянс Конечно они так АНС - это более
French Yes
французская Да
NS Well yes well Well maybe the devil knows
НС Ну да а Ну возможно Чёрт его знает да
yes well to be honest I’m not English
ну честно говоря я не англичанин
after all of
всё-таки
course English is good but I’m
конечно английский это хорошо но я
just me  I’ve been teaching Lithuanian since the very
просто я литовский преподаю с самого
university Yes, I’ve been teaching English in Lithuania for 18 years now,
университета Да Английский уже 18 лет
in 2 years we’ll
преподаю в Литве у нас через 2 года
be
будет
teaching for the 20th year, I’m teaching because I myself am a
двадцатое преподаю потому что я сам
Russian speaker in Lithuania and I teach
русскоязычный в Литве и я преподаю
English for
английский язык для
Russian speakers. That’s great;
русскоязычных Здорово здорово не
English isn’t really needed. Well, without
английский нужен на самом деле Ну да без
it there’s nothing
него никуда
really
неча правда скам
I wouldn’t say scam either in Portugal. There, not
тоже я бы не сказал в Португалии Там не
everyone was able to talk to me in
все смогли со мной поговорить на
English, they didn’t understand it, well,
английском не понимали они его вот ну
someone understood it, some Portuguese
кто-то понимал там некоторые португальцы
still understood, but I’m a pensioner. I
всё-таки понимали а так вот пенсионеры я
tried to talk to my grandfather there in English, too.
Вот пытался там на английском тоже с
some kind of
дедушкой поговорить ни в какой либо
Portuguese or Let's go, this is how it
португальский либо Давай иди вот так вот
turns out What native
получается Какие вы знаете исконно
English
английские
names
имена английские
do you know English names Mark knows the same as
имена чрт его знает Марк по тоже как
English Mark is more Mark is a
английска Марк это более Марк это
biblical name TSI some kind of I don’t
библейское имя тси какая-нибудь там не
know that’s what their names are
знаю вот как там их зовут
also sa Well yes them  there they have different names, as
ещё са Ну да их там по-разному как
long as they don’t call them
только не зовут там
George, they are
Джордж им
Anglo-Saxon names. But John is
англосаксонские имена А вот Джон
probably John - this is John, this is a biblical
наверное Джон - это Иоанн это библейское
name, like
имя как
Ivan Paul, this is Paul Paul, this is Paul, this is a
Иван пол это Павел пол это Павел это
biblical name, Paul Paul, this is in different
библейское имя Поль Павел это в разных
names, I really like Paul Makart, yes. Well, here you go
именах по очень нравится пол макарт да А
what an original Anglo-Saxon name is
ну вот какое искона англосаксонское имя
an original
искона
Anglo-Saxon
англосаксонское
name, well, richar is such a good name
намер ну ричар такое хорошее имя
really Oh, so for a discount, you don’t even
действительно О так на скидку так и не
remember so
припомни так
yes Beatles I like what does Beatles
да Beatles Мне нравится а что Beatles
mean in translation from English Well,
означает в переводе с английского Ну так
since it’s written there, in my opinion, it doesn’t
как там пишется оно по-моему ничего и не
mean anything at all Beatles
означает вообще Beatles
Beetles
Жуки
Well, they are spelled
пи ну они по-другому пишутся кстати вот
differently by the way, that's the way they are for me. No, the thing is, look at the Beatle yourself, where you come from, you know Well, Liverpool Well, Liverpool You know that in England there are different
знаете что в Англии есть разные
dialects Yeah, right up to Yes, right up
диалекты Угу Вот и вплоть до Да вплоть
to the reform of
до реформы
1488  Yes, there were different spellings,
1488 года Да там было разное написание
different spellings, then when they unified a
разное написание потом когда объединили
single spelling in England, they adopted it, and
единое правописание в Англии приняли вот
since then, some regions
с тех пор некоторые регионы используют
also use their own grammatical features,
ещё свои грамматические особенности
so they could write with deviations
поэтому они могли писать с отклонениями
from the official one, it’s not their
от официального это ж у них не
official name, but for
официальное название а для
themselves, maybe you’re with Vadu then  you
себя о Может вы тогда с ваду так хорошо
understand everything so well. Maybe you can
во всём разбираетесь Может вы тогда мне
also tell me at the same time how best to change the
ещё заодно подскажете как лучше поменять
oil seal on the rear axle in a Zhiguli
сальник на заднем мосту в Жигулях
six, but I
шестёрки вот нет я вот в этих в
don’t understand these cars at all, but I
автомобилях я вообще не разбираюсь а на
have a car, I
машине есть
go to a service station
я заезжаю в станцию технического
and there I’m good too
обслуживания и там мне Ну тоже хорошо
you see,
видите
you can sing that you can sing on the guitar
выводите что что вы умеете на гитаре
Yes, all sorts of different things there, that’s
петь Да всякое разное там вот вот напер
where I liked it, I wrote my own song,
там понравилось е свою песенку
you can play the guitar for a change, that’s
сочинил можете ця перемен сыграть на
not what I don’t play, but I want my own little
гитаре не это я не играю А вот хочу свою
song
песенку мочку
about a girl about a girl, well, I understand you
про дево про девочку а ну я понял Вам
In short, you  only to compose songs there are
Короче вы только песенки сочинять есть
guys who go out with girls And there are
парни которые с девочками гуляют А есть
some Sochi songs Well, unfortunately,
которые песенки Сочи Ну к сожалению
since the second doesn’t work out, I
поскольку не получается второе
have to do the first, I understood yes
приходится первое я понял да
[music] [
[музыка]
One
One
applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music]
[музыка]
and
and
will
will
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
on F Girl will
on F Girl will
show Yes
show Yes
[music]
[музыка]
AS
AS
applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music]
[музыка]
Girl
Girl
Will Yes
Will Yes
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Girl
Girl
[music]
[музыка]
will
will
Well, I liked this song, to be honest,
Ну такая мне песенка понравилась честно
maybe it inspired
говоря вот видно может быть подвигло
me  the fact that you were sick with Covid just
меня то что ты болел ковидом как раз вот
about the red-haired girl nku write Well, yes And
про рыжую девочку нку сочинить Ну да А
when you were sick with Covid you composed
когда ты болел ковидом ты сочинил
a song about the red-haired girl yes Well yes Oh, you
песенку про рыжую девочку да Ну да Ой вы
should have seen that I did this with networks here, this is a
бы видели что я се сетями тут сделал это
nightmare there is a question, such an indiscreet question
кошмар там вопрос так нескромный вопрос
you are 18 years old  to
вам 18 лет
us to us I beg your pardon, there are actually 38
нам нам Прошу прощения есть вообще-то 38
tons, do you live on your own or with your parents? Well, what about
т живёте сами или с родителями Ну как с
your mother and the cable? Well, the cable is somewhere
мамой и с кабелём Ну кабель где-то у
there; my mother
меня там ещё мама в соседней комнате
lives in the next room or in the
живёт или в этой
same room. Well, how does she even live in an apartment,
же Ну как она вообще живёт в квартире
that means in  room How to understand that in the
вот значит в комнате Как понять что в
room we are generally free people, we
комнате вообще-то мы люди свободные мы
do not restrict anyone, well, you and your mother
никого не ограничиваем ну вы вы с мамой
live in the same apartment, yes, as I understand it,
в одной квартире живёте да я так понимаю
well, yes, what is it that I don’t have a girl
Ну да а что такого у ме девочки нету
question What if mom wants to bring
вопрос А если мама хочет привести
some friend to sit  Well,
какого-то там друга посидеть Ну как она
she’s not ashamed of you, she doesn’t want to. She’s 60 years old
не стесняется вас она не хочет Ей 60 лет
and disabled, so she doesn’t want to. Do you
и она инвалид поэтому она не хочет А вы
want something? I want a girl or something, home. It’s
хотите хочу чего девочку что ли домой дн
better to bring a Girl to her, yes, it’s better, I
привести лучше к ней да лучше так мне
also like blondes. Maybe a blonde, but
ещё блондинки нравятся Может блондинку а
to her like you have there  that it hasn’t been cleaned or
к ней типа у тебя там что не убрано или
mom will get in the way and something in
мама мешать будет да что-то как-то
general I think that I don’t want to go home KSB Well,
вообще я считаю что не хочу домой ксб Ну
girls, there’s probably
девочки же наверное жилплощадь наверно
some kind of living space, especially if she’s also a redhead, she’s
какая-то есть особенно если ещё и рыжая
not a red-haired girl who lives on the street.
она же не на улице живёт рыжая девочка
Listen, it seems to me that you  You’re a little
Слушай мне кажется что ты немножко
overestimating your value, I
переоцениваешь свою ценность ты Я
understand that you’re such an awesome guitarist.
понимаю что ты такой офигенный гитарист
Well, like, you were still
Да ну типа ты ещё
sorting out your living space. Well, yes, well,
перебирала с жилплощади Ну да да ну
but why don’t you overestimate anything?
только че не надо ничего переоценивать
I paid the money and went to a brothel there,
вон деньги заплатил и пошл там в бордель
that’s where you want redheads, you want blondes,
вот там хочешь рыжие хочешь блондинки
at least some, I understood, I understood everything.
хоть какие всё понял понял А деньги у
you have money, you are what you work for, and I work as a
тебя есть ты кем работаешь А я работаю
driver, what do you
водителем что водишь как вот заработаю
drive? I’ll earn money there for a week, then I’ll go for an hour.
там недельку поработаю потом на часик
And after that, there’s no money again, I
схожу Вот и после этого денег нет опять
have to work as a
надо работать
sex worker. Well, I don’t care about the girls yet, I
половой Ну пока мне не до девочек надо
still need to fix the car
машину ещё починить там
there. There’s another problem here, by the way, mom  I
Тут ещё проблема тут кстати маме денег
have to give money away. Oh
должен самое ещё отдавать деньги надо Ой
yes I need to earn money. How old are you
да Надо заработать ди Сколько тебе лет
again, by the way, I’m not just talking about girls
ещё раз я кстати не только про девочек
honestly how old are you again 38 I
честно сколько тебе лет ещё раз 38 Я же
said 38 phrase at 38 years old I still owe my mother
сказал 38 фраза в 38 лет я ещё маме
money, this is of course a masterpiece Well,
денег должен это конечно шедевр Ну да
what can I do?  By the way, I have a
что делать А у меня кстати есть песенка
masterpiece song too stop stop stop stop no no
шедевральная тоже стоп стоп стоп стоп не
no Wait Hello hello about the girls Hello
не не Подожди Алло алло про девочек Алло
No no no Come on without a song New
Не не не надо Давай без песни Новое
dimension let's not Here let's talk about the
измерение давай не Вот вот давай про
New dimension we won't have songs Let
Новое измерение мы не будем песни Давай
's talk like this without songs O'  kay, well, it’s
мы так поговорим без песен О'кей ну
somehow boring without songs, to be
что-то как-то без песен как-то скучно
honest, I want some songs,
честно говоря хочется песенок каких-то
but how can it be without dogs? What, what, what do
да то как же без пес А что что что у
you have there for so many books on the shelf, what kind of
тебя там за столько книг на стеллаже что
books are there, but he knows, I don’t know there in  these are
там за книги а знает я не знаю там в это
even your books
даже твои книги
Well, maybe
Ну может и
my SS, maybe
мои СС может и
your box is where it is, wait, you’re
тво ящик какой сде подожди п ты у себя у
sitting in your house Well, yes, I made this box there myself,
сидиш Ну да это ящик там сделал сам тоже
too. Well, you know, I made
также Вот я знаете вот сделал ножницы
toy scissors, I still
игрушечные у меня ещ
have it, show me this
есть а покажите ящик этот
locking box  well, come on now,
запирающий ну давай сечас
and you see here, this is what you can open
а вон видишь тут это самое можно открыть
for this, you need to look here Then then, this one
для этого надо вот Вот Потом значит эту
here like this and closer I don’t see the
вот сюда вот так а ближе Я не вижу
mechanism, bring it closer to the camera
механизм поднесите его к камере ближе
because And yes, it takes a long time to shoot there Well,
потому что А да там снимать долго Ну
take it off Well, I’ll
снимите Ну я
wait
подожду
Oh no,  somehow I don’t want to Well, here
Ой не что-то как-то не хочется Ну вот
then it’s stuck back here
тут потом обратно вот сюда
Well, well, there’s
засовывается Ну да
a lot here then back BC it’s
сюда много потом обратно ВС это
somehow better to show something else
ставить-то как-то лучше чтоб другое
then And what else I have is
покажу тогда А что у меня ещё-то есть
interesting, well, you have toy scissors
интересно ну ножницы игрушечные у ва у
I think it was an untucked T-shirt
вас по-моему незаправленная майка была
or something Or it seemed to me that there were
или как Или мне показалось есть
toy ones Well, there are a lot of things there, of course
игрушечные Ну там много чего конечно
I have all sorts of invented ones,
есть у меня там всяких изобретенный вот
I like to invent something a little oh I also
люблю немножко что-то изобретать о ещё
made this one now I’ll show you he also made
этот сделал сейчас покажу он ещё сделал
such a pencil case
такой пенал
here’s a very necessary thing at home pencil case Yes there
вот очень нужная дома вещь пенал Да вон
here If you can put a lock here, I
тут Если что може замочек сюда вешать на
don’t hang it on it. But it looks like a
его не вешаю А так вот похоже на
mousetrap here.
мышеловку тут
Needle files. Well, what are
надфили надфили Ну да а что такое
needle files? For example, I understand that they’re hardened, they look like Chinese. Well, they’re hardened, so there are grooves here for the files. Yes, they’re on Aliexpress.  you can’t
для надфилей Да это на алиэкспрессе не
buy it Well, why would I rather do it myself then
купишь Ну да зачем я лучше Сам тогда
what else to sing nah
сделаю чем ещё са чем поть нах
aessa Ate pose How did you furnish it,
аэсса Ате поза Как вы обставил ещё что
maybe you made some kind of shelving in
может вы стеллаж какой-то сделали в
the room or else I can’t and I can’t and I do
комнате не то этого я не могу и не могу
n’t
и не
want I can’t and I don’t want  It’s interesting to
хочу не могу и не хочу ине Интересно
me somehow, why should I
как-то мне это зачем же мне что-то
do something if I don’t want to do something? And by
делать если что-то делать не хочу вот А
the way, now I’ll show you what I did,
ещё я кстати сейчас покажу что я сделал
I also have toy movies. That’s what I
вон ещё у меня есть игрушечные кины Вот
was doing, I was doing something at home from a
делал было дела что-то дома из
piece of wood. Well  he doesn’t look like Well, please
деревяшки Ну он не похоже Ну пожалуйста
Well, there’s a hole, how doesn’t it look
Ну что дырочка есть как не
like just a second Now wait a minute, he’s
похоже сейчас секундочку Сейчас погоди
gone somewhere over there, look, you see there
куда-то подевался вон тут смотри видишь
he is, he’s getting
вон он вот он влезает сюда
into those
во те с
things here I don’t have an attic Well, keep in mind that
чемно У меня нету чердака Ну Имей в виду
everything’s fine with this, Otherwise  I would
с а с этим всё нормально Иначе бы я бы
n’t do all this if it were
этого всего не сделал бы когда было бы
abnormal, you’re not registered somewhere
ненормально ты не стоишь на учёте где-то
in a dispensary, I don’t stand and I don’t lie and I don’t
в диспансере не не стою и не лежу и не
sit like that, but you’re using some kind of not-
сижу так а употребляешь какие-то не
quite-bad stuff, that is, that’s your natural
совсем убля то есть это твоё природное
state,
состояние да
yeah Well, that’s normal  You're mocking
Ну да что нормально Ты издеваешься надо
me, but it's not me. I'm clarifying. I'm clarifying, you're
мной да не я Уточняю я Уточняю ты надо
mocking me.
мною издеваешься
What kind of person are you
Какой же ты
then, how do you think whose
тогда как ты считаешь чей
Crimea is? It’s
Крым
not clear whose it’s definitely not mine.
Дат тут уже непонятно чей точно не мой
How do you feel about the fact that Russia has attacked
Как ты относишься к тому что Россия нала
Ukraine? I
Украину никак не
don’t have any relationship with this, but
отношусь к этому отношений не
who is to blame for this war, what do you
имею а кто виноват в этой войне как ты
think?
считаешь
Oh, I don’t know who is to blame; who is right to
Ой я не знаю уже кто виноват кто прав
judge; it’s not for us; but the cart is not there;
судить Не нам Да только воз ина не там
he’s just
он как раз
Krylov, like in that fable; Swan, Cancer and
Крылов как в той басне Лебедь рак и
Pike; Okay, we need to play in FSN;
щука Ладно надо в фсн сыграть
by the way, this is the same thing; this is also necessary
кстати это самое вот это тоже надо
play
поиграть
nku yes, how is she by the way T G major
нку да ну-ка как она кстати Т Соль [__]
[music]
[музыка]
Love stop stop stop stop stop look
Love стоп стоп стоп стоп стоп смотри
Hello All hello dude There is
Алло Ал алло чувак Есть
[music]
[музыка]
topic Let's write to my Telegram right
тема Давай пись на мий Telegram прямо
now axis vin a
зараз ось вин а
pok tse duzhe  and very respectfully YouTube has taken
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ODS in your ban and I
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
don’t show too many videos to people at all times, I don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for this purpose, so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
Mali has an operational link to
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
write directly at the same time, and while there in teleg
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в teleg
okm video also tezh tsikava and korisna
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and  we'll
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
with
с